Charles Bukowski papers, 1958-1988
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series II: Poetry and Prose Manuscripts, 1971-1978
  - Poetry Manuscripts. 1970-1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    "I didn't what time it was until I met you"
    "the icecream people"
    "ONE WITH DANTE"
    "THE ONE WHO COULDN'T MISS"
    "Poem for an Errand Boy in the Year 1941"
    "poem for Dante"
    "Song for this Softly-Sweeping Sorrow" (two versions)
    "tv"
    "an unhappy lady"
    '"UPON AN INVITATION TO A PARTY IN WEST L.A., WHICH I DIDN'T GO TO"
    "Venice, Calif."
    "wet night"
    "wrong crapper"
    "yes,yes"
    "crisscross under sideways"
    "dig me a ditch"
    "I HAVE TAKEN THE PLACE OF THE STARVING ARTIST I USED TO BE (for Charles Bukowski)"
    "now she hates me" (two versions)
    "Africa, Paris, Greece"
    "the Apprentices"
    "the big ride"
    "the crunch"
    "F.F. (for Graham and Claire)"
    "how good sleep is before having to walk down any street --"
    ""I cause some remarkable creativity"
    "interviews"
    "My ol' drinking buddies..."
    "my toilet"
    "$180 out"
    "private first class"
    "women at my dresser mirror"
    "yellow cab"
  - Poetry Manuscripts. No Date (Box 9, Folder 5)
    "Action down on the Corner"
    "All God's Children"
    "and it's shady too"
    "AND MOZART LIVED ON BIRD STREET"
    "another poem for another lady"
    "as the angels shine their bungholes"
    "the best love poem I can write at the moment"
    "a bit of early morning action"
    "bloodred"
    "BLUE MOON, OH BLEWEEWW MOOOOON HOW I ADORE YOU"
    "Bob Dylan"
    "Born to Lose"
    "broken ass like a cherry seed down the throat"
    "clown poem: I"
    "constitutional rights"
    "crowds"
    "DEATH"
    "down at Prarie and Century this is where we live"
    "dragging around the heights with typewriter fingers"
    "18th and Grand"
    "an exaggeration"
    "50 watercolors"
    "$5.95"
    "flie song"
    "FRANKLY D. WAS AN OLD CRIPPLE JUST LIKE LIFE"
    "the Gigolo"
    "go to your grave cleanly--"
    "a groupie"
    "A HAPPY MAN"
    "haul ass, wonder woman"
    "hug the dark"
    "I can hear the sound of human lives being ripped to pieces"
    ""I got my diploma"
    "I LOSE SOME MORE TOY BALLOONS"
    "I PISS UPON THE WORKS OF MEN"
    "I sometimes have shit stains in my underwear"
    "junk"
    "the knife waltz"
    "LAUNDRY"
    "a lazy afternoon"
    "a lifetime report from an agent from Mars who lived almost his total life on earth"
    "little magazines and poetry chapbooks"
    "livin' in a great big way"
    "Love is a midget"
  - Poetry Manuscripts. No Date (Box 9, Folder 6)
    "the mad poet"
    "MAN AND WOMAN IN BED AT 10:30 P.M."
    "mean black kitty"
    "mons of honey drown the lark hahaha"
    "my hump-backed laughing soul"
    "my instructor"
    "no man is an island"
    "o.d."
    "on shooting"
    "one for old Marv between the popcorn and the beer--"
    "ONE FOR THE SHOESHINE MAN"
    "one night stands"
    "the only mistress"
    "THE ORIGINAL"
    "THE PAINTER"
    "THE POETRY READING"
    "Polish Sausage"
    "the reason:"
    "REXALL CUT-RATE, 4:30 P.M."
    "Robinson Jeffers and love"
    "The Scale"
    "sometimes even putting a nickle into a parking meter feels fairly good--"
    ""Song of this old man"
    "star-fuckers"
    "stillness"
    "tables"
    "THIS ONE POET"
    "thoughts on an evening when grey walls breathe and huff:"
    "3 pairs of panties"
    "the triangle"
    "unleaded"
    "Upon Going to bed with a copy of Cosmopolitan"
    "A VISITOR FROM CANADA"
    "The Way It Works"
    "we are all the residue of a democratic society"
    "what they want"
    "what we did"
    "with grace and all the luck of the way"
    "you, back in the ninth row, let me tell you something"
    Incomplete Poems: Last Pages of Three Poems
  - Prose Manuscripts: Notes of a Dirty Old Man. 1970-1975 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    With the exception of poetry, individual pieces in Notes are untitled. The first sentence, or part thereof, is used for indentification. Includes:
    "It was in Washinton, D.C., a private party..."
    "Down around Sunset, about Sunset and Wilton..."
    "Gary picked up the phone."
    "Harry bought a newspaper and walked into the travel agency..."
    "He came into town one night dressed all in black..."
  - Prose Manuscripts: Notes of a Dirty Old Man. 1971-1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    "I awakened at 8:30 a.m."
    "I met the Crotties quite by accident."
    "I suppose one of the most amazing and startling acts..."
    "Marty drove up the lane, parked the car and got out."
    "They were both seven years old..."
    Poetry: "Eddie Belmonte," "little theatre Hollywood," "the concrete world," "IN THE CENTER OF THEIR VERY ACTION," "no more of these men..." (this poem is incomplete and there may originally have been other titles).
    "Outside of La Paz, about an hour and a half..."
    "Pete was 13, a difficult age they say..." (first eight pages)
    "The ambulance was full but they found me a place on top..." (first and second pages)
  - Other Prose Manuscripts. 1971-1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Untitled, incomplete (first page only) essay on d.a. levy, 1971
    "The Outsider", tribute to Jon Web (incomplete, pp. 5-9, published in The Wormwood Review #45, 1972)
    "The L.A. Scene...", 1971-1972
    "A note on these Poems", on Al Prudy, November 24, 1976
    "YOU KISSED LILY", 1977
    "break-in", three copies, no date
    HAIRY FIST TALES, "Two Hands Are Better Than One"
    "contributors"
    Part 17, pp. 50-54 of a longer work
- Series III: Magazine Appearances, 1966-1977
  - Abyss, v.3, #1, Spring: "POET IN RESIDENCE," "NOBODY WANTS TO HEAR YOUR TROUBLES," and "the misfit." 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Adam, v.15, #5, October, p. 11: "Dirty Old Man Confesses." 1971 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Adam, v.16, #1, February, p. 13: "Animal Crackers in My Soup." 1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Adios Againe, #7, p. 14: "Buk at Bodega," by Pierette Jordan. 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Aldebaran Review, #9, August: At Terror Street and Agony Way, review, author unknown. 1970 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - The American Poetry Review, v.4, #2, p. 11: "B," and "Drooling Madness at St. Liz." 1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Ampersand, March: "Confessions of a Misanthrope." 1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Amphora, #8, pp. 20-24: "Louis-Ferdinand Destouches," "Death," "Winterlost," "pain is a flower..." (first line), "All the Sacred Christs that Never Arrive." 1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Aunt Harriet's, November, pp. 2-5: "love," " a plausible finish," "pull a string, a puppet moves...," "An Almost Made up Poem about a Lady Who Has Vanished from My Mailbox." 1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - the avalanche, #2, Fall: "Guilt Obsession behind a Cloud of Rockets." 1967 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - the avalanche, #3, Summer: "living." 1967 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Bachy, v.1, #3, July, pp. 109-111: "Purple and Black," "My Brother Ernest Hemingway," and "Measurements from the Creation Coffin." 1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Bartleby's Review, v.1, #1: "Burning," "40,000 flies," and "We Can't." 1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Bartleby's Review, v.1, #1, pp. 14-15: "ah." 1972 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Bastard Angel, #3, Fall, pp. 46-47: "the blue head of death," and "blue cheese and chili peppers." 1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Bear, #1: "the flu," and "The Answer." 1971 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Blitz, #1: "86'd," "On Going Out to Get the Mail," and "Spain Sits Like a Hidden Flower in My Coffeepot." 1965? (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Brand "X", #5, May: "My Faithful Indian Servant." 1962 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - CQ (California State Poetry Society, Quarterly), v.1, #2, Winter, pp. 2-4, 46: "the ordinary care of the world," "he learned it from Gertie," and "The Movie." 1972 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - California Librarian, v.31, #4, October, p. 246: "the poetry reading." 1970 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Camels Coming, #1, May: two letters from C.B. to Richard Morris (editor). 1972 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Cave #4, November, pp. 4, 8-10, 12-13: "The Hippies and the Killer," "down by the sea, the beautiful sea," "A Hot Tip on the Future," "Ya Know Beethoven Conducted His Last Symphony While Almost Totally Deaf?," "down the silver river with one shoe off," "Notes on a Dirty Old Man (An Introduction to Charles Bukowski)," by G.J. Melling. 1973 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Chicago Review, v.24, #3, Winter, pp. 128-129, and 131: "notes upon reading the Christian Science Monitor," The glass fly," "there are demons in all our heavens," and "zoo." 1972 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Choice, #2, p. 48: "9 rings." 1962 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Choice, #5, p. 32: "People as Flowers," and "To Hell with Robert Schumann." 1967 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Chouteau Review, v.2, #1,Summer, p. 61: "ask the butterfly," and "bathtub." 1977 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - City Lights Journal, #4, p. 43: "A Scene of Temperate Indifference." 1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Coast, v.17, #2, February: "I'd Like a Mermaid." 1976 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Coastlines, #20 (v.5, #4), p. 12: "Warble In--." 1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Congress, #1, p. 25: "The Way the Dead Love (from a "novel in progress") ." 1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Copkiller, #1, January: "The Status Q. for Me and Yew." 1968 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Corduroy, v.1, #3, p. 8: "beefrice." 1972 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Cotyledon, #2(?), pp. 8-9: "those sons of bitches," "a little bit of EXCITEMENT," "A Hero's Death" "Robert Ryan: American Matador," "the virgin of the bulls," "song," and "An Interesting Night." No Date (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Crazy Horse, #12, Autumn: "You Don't Know What Love Is (an evening with Charles Bukowski)", by Raymond Carver. 1972 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Creem, v.7, #5, October: "Jaggernaut" and "Wild Horse on a Plastic Phallus." 1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Dare, v.4, #8, November, p. 45: "the moment of truth" with a short commentary by Hale Chatfield. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - De Humanities, v.1, #3, Summer: "an unusual place," "arena," "those sons of bitches," quote from inside front cover. 1966 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Desperado, #9, November: " For C.B." by Linda King. 1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Dodeca, #16 (v.2, #8), August: "Bukowski in New York: One Six-pack Isn't Enough" by Tom Jackrell. 1976 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Down Here, v.1, #1, p. 8: "The Bukowski-McNamara Letters" correspondence between C.B. and Tom McNamara. 1966 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Down Here, v.1, #2, Spring, p. 87: "McNamara Letter" letter from C.B. to Tom McNamara and two letters from T.M. to C.B. 1967 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - dust, v.1, #4, Fall, pp. 75-76: "ice for the eagles." 1964 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - dust, v.1, #4, Winter, p. 26: "Uraguay or Hell." 1965 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - dust, v.2, #4, (#8), Spring/Summer: "A Fine Day and the World Looks Good." 1966 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Earth, #1: "freedom," and Confessions of a Man Insane Enough to Live with Beasts, review, author unknown. 1965 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Earth, #2: "upon/that which makes the..." (first lines), "I Love You," "3 lovers," "I am read to," "the people" and The Earth Rose. 1966 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - The Eight Pager, series 1, part 3: "The Stupid Are Best at the Cruelties" and "The Sex-obsessed Ladies Walking by Me after Work." No Date (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - The Emerson Review, v.1, #1, Winter, pp. 8-9, 11: "Experience," "Weather Report," and "Part of an Ordinary Day of an Inordinate Man." 1963 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Entrails, #4, July-August, p. 48: "the faces are gnawing at my wall but have not yet come in...." 1967 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Entrails Anthology (The Human Voice, v. 3, #4, Winter), pp. 16-17: "God," "tomorrow there will be a letter in the mail" (first line). 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Event, v.1, #3, Winter, pp. 40, 42, 44: "I Saw an Old Fashioned Whore Today," "The Sun Is the God of the Attic," and "the original." 1972 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Event, v.2, #1, pp. 40, 42: "Notes upon the Flaxen Aspect," and "Use of the Continuous Present." 1972(?) (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Event, v.2, #2, Fall, pp. 50-51: "Hot," and a painting of C.B. by Dini Evanier. 1972 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Event, v.2, #3, Spring: "A Letter from Charles Bukowski" addressed to David Evanier (editor). 1973 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Event, v.3, #3, Summer, pp. 14, 16, 18, 20-21: "All God's Children Got Troubles," "I Can't Stay in the Same Room with that Woman for Five Minutes," "I get all the latest hit tunes/free" (first lines), "You Do It While You're Killing Flies," "Dragging around the Heights with Typewriter Fingers," and "The Artist." 1973 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Evergreen Review, v.11, #50, December, p. 75: "Men's Crapper." 1967 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Evergreen Review, v.13, #63, February, p. 44: "Even the Sun Was Afraid." 1969 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Evergreen Review, v.13, #70, September, p. 41: "The Birth, Life, and Death of an Underground Newspaper." 1969 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Evergreen Review, v.14, #74, January, p. 55: "The Day We Talked about James Thurber." 1970 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Evergreen Review, v.14, #79, June, p. 37: " Soup, Cosmos and Tears." 1970 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Everyman, Summer, pp. 79-80, 82, 84: "A Hot Day in Los Angeles," "the reading," "the drunk tank judge," "Directions, Instructions, and Signs to the Indolent, the Bored, and the Insufficient," and "panties." 1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Fervent Valley, #1, Spring: "Power Failure," and "For Those Who Put Themselves upon Me." 1972 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Fervent Valley, #2, Summer: "six." 1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Fireweed, v.1, #3, Spring, p. 26: "rip-off." 1976 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Fling, v.14, #4, September, p.15: Hairy Fist Tales and "no quickies," and "remember." 1971 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Fling, v.14, #5, November, p. 23: Hairy Fist Tales and "The Looney Ward." 1971 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Fling, v.14, #6, January, p. 20: Hairy Fist Tales and "dancing mind." 1972 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Florida Education, v.42, #1, September, p. 16: "The Priest and the Matador." 1963 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Florida Education, v.42, #9, May, pp. 16-17: "the day it rained at the los angeles county museum," "side of the sun," "SUICIDE," "the tragedy of the leaves," "LOVE & DEATH & FAME," "old man, dead in a room," "horray say the roses," "THE KINGS ARE GONE." 1965 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - The Galley Sail, v.2, #2 (#6), June, p. 12: "Conversation in a Cheap Room." 1960 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Gambit, v.10, #11, November, pp. 8, 10-11: "style," "the rat," "Will the Real Mr. Bukowski Please Sit Down (To Know Him is Not to Love Him)" by Liza Williams, "The Name's Familiar" on Peter Hackford and film Bukowski, author unknown. 1973 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Gasolin 23, #6, October: "Junkies," "Bier," and "Bie Wind und Wetter." 1978 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Gay Sunshine, #18, June-July, p.6: "Harold Norse: an Interview" has section on C.B. 1973 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Ghost-Dance, p. 14: "yellow sun yellow cat eye kitchen floor." No Date (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - The Grande Ronde Review, Fall: "The Soi-disant Plaintiffs," review of Run with the Hunted by A. Frederic Franklin. 1964 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - The Grande Ronde Review, #6: "the hairy fist, and love will die." 1966 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Grist, #9, p.4: "hot" and "fire." No Date (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Half N' Half, April: "Shoelace." 1971 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Hanging Loose, #15, August, pp. 3-4: "a threat to my immortality" and "The Garbageman." 1971 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - The Harrison Street Review, #2, pp. 10-11: "Title: on Living with a Big Fat Whore who loves you..." and set of drawings. No Date (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - The Harrison Street Review, #3, pp. 10-11: "Roses are Red Violets are Blue," "the Great Poet," and "One Night Stands." 1972 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Hearse, #10: "The Days Run away like Wild Horses over the Hills." 1969 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Hearse, #11: "On Getting Famous and Being Asked: Can you Recite? Can You Be There at Nine?." 1969 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Hearse, #14: "Sheets." 1970 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Hearse, #15: "Vallejo" and "The End of the Funhouse." 1971 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Hearse, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    #17: "The Automobiles of De Longpre: (signed: For Linda King from Her Great Lover-Poet. Charles Bukowski 12-30-72)
    "The Beast"
    "On the Wagon"
    "Share the Pain"
    "The Golfers"
    "B.W."
    "Man and Woman in Bed at Ten P.M."
    "You Just Imagine"
    "The Mockingbird"
    "The Sex Fiends"
    "I Was Clean Anyhow, I Think"
  - The Hiram Poetry Review, #1, Fall-Winter, p. 8-9: "The Great One" and "sensible brush, sleeping/flower, I awaken" (first lines). 1966 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - The Hiram Poetry Review, #5, Fall-Winter, p.6: "Just Another Wind " and The Human Voice (see Entrails Anthology). 1968 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Hustler, v.3, #6, December, p. 40: "Interview: Charles Bukowski, Dialog with a Dirty Old Man." 1976 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Hustler, v.3, #9, p. 66: "The Big Dope Reading." 1977 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Hustler, v. 4, #1, July, p.78: "Workout." 1977 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Hustler, v.4 #4, October, p. 52: "3 Chickens." 1977 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Hustler, v.4, #11, May, p. 92: "An Affair of Very Little Importance." 1978 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Intermission, v.1, #23, December, p. 17: letter from C.B. to Gene Cole (editor). 1965 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Intermission, v.2 #29, March, p. 13: "Notes on an Underground Existence." 1966 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Intermission, Yearbook, p.1: "A Rambling Essay on Poetics and the Bleeding Life Written While Drinking a Six-pack (Tall)." 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Intrepid, #7, March: "Men's Crapper." 1967 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Intrepid, #8, June: letter from C.B. to Allen DeLoach (editor). 1967 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Intrepid, #9, December: "Poem for the Death of an American Serviceman in Vietman," "A Bad Night--Blame the Bourbon," and "From the Dept. of English." 1967 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Intrepid, #11-12, March, pp. 54, 56: "don't worry baby, I'll get it," "notebook," and "Poem to Charles Bukowski" by Jack Micheline (this is a manuscript poem written inside back cover). 1969 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Intrepid, #18-19, p. 124: "Hey Bukowski" by James Silver. 1971 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Intrepid, #23-24, Summer-Fall, p. 31: "Royal. tab clear. tab set. mar rel. back space." 1972 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Invisible City, #1, February, pp. 3-6. 1971 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    "here"
    "style"
    "ah"
    "Rolled Again"
    "You Might as Well Kiss Your Ass Goodbye"
    "Songs of Death"
    "The Last Days of the Suicide Kid"
    "5 Men in Black Passing My Window"
    "the bums at Phillipe's"
  - Invisible City, #2, June, p. 15: "last act," "the American Flag Shirts," "drinking," "A Most Dark Night in April," and "Upon 2 Deaths." 1970 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Invisible City, #3, November, p. 9: "The Writer," "2 carnations," "pleasure song," and "the shower." 1971 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Invisible City, #5, February, p. 15: "The Hatred for Hemingway." 1972 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Invisible City, #7, October, p. 15: "one more farewell," "the bells," and "madness." 1972 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Kauri, #9, July-August, p. 9: "Bukowski" by James Gove. 1965 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Kauri, # 10, September-October, pp. 1, 3: "A Party Here--Machineguns, Tanks an Army Fighting Against Men on Rooftops" and a letter from C.B. to Will Inman (editor). 1965 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Knight, v.9, #7, October, p.17: "Henry Miller Lives In Pacific Palisades and I Live on Skid Row Writing about Sex." 1972 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Komiks, #1, p.2: two excerpts from C.B. letters. 1965 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Komiks, #3: two excerpts from C.B. letter. 1965? (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - The Lampeter Muse, v.3, #3, Fall, p.4: "A Literary Romance." 1968 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Laugh Literary and Man the Humping Guns, v.1, #3, February, edited by C.B. and Neeli Cherry: "The Time I Knocked out Ernest Hemingway and Was Discovered as a New Literary Giant" and five excerpts from letters, D.B. for Neeli Cherry. 1971 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Lemming, #1, Winter, pp. 5, 7: "The Savior" and "I like that." 1971 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Litmus Loadstone, #11: "The Hairy Hairy Fist" and "Love Will Die." No Date (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - The Little Magazine, v.6, #1, Spring, pp. 14-15: "Bullshit Pain," and "The People." 1972 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - The Little Magazine, v.6, #2-3, Summer-Fall, pp. 25-26: "The Brainless Eyes" and "The Sun, the Bushes, the Hell of It--." 1972 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Madrona, #2, Fall, p. 16: "The Best Love Poem I Can Write at the Moment." 1971 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Mag, #2, Winter, pp. 1-4: "Engraving Found upon the Back of a Bill Sent to Me by the Southern California Gas Company, Oct. 12th, 1971," "balling," "I found this atomic stockpile," and "After the Party." 1972 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Mag, #4, Summer, pp. 65, 68, 69: "pop pop pop," "A Harder Knocker" and "the ants." 1972 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Mag, #6, Summer-Fall: "the best love poem I can write at the moment." 1973 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Mano-Mano, #2, July, pp. 48-49: "The Angels of Sunday," and "ha ha ha ha ha, ha ha." 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Meatball, #2, p. 31: A Bukowski Sampler, review, author unknown. No Date (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Meatball, #8: "chilled green," "Several Feet by Three and One Half Feet Tall," "my special insanity," "story and poem," and "In This Whirling Pot of Piss Some Songs Are Born." 1971 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - The MidAtlantic Review, v.1, #1, Summer, pp. 15-17: "the lady poetess with long blonde hair and long silver gown, standing tall and explaining to her audience how the muse CAME," "Big Max," and "KRAZNICK." 1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Moonstones, #2: "A Man Gets Tired." 1966 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - The New York Quarterly, #7, Summer, pp. 26-28: "The Dogs Bark Knives," "Have You Ever Kissed a Panther?" and "The Good Life at O'Hare Airport." 1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - The New York Quarterly, #8, Autumn, pp. 27-28, 68: "Notes on a Door-Knocker," "Inverted Love Song" and photo of C.B. by Claude Powell. 1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - The New York Quarterly, #9, Winter, pp. 49-50: "style" and "My Literary Fly." 1972 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - The New York Quarterly, #10, Spring, pp. 44, 46: "He Wrote in Lonely Blood" and "Law." 1972 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - The New York Quarterl y, #11, Summer, p. 118: announcement of an award for C.B. 1972 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - The New York Quarterly, #12, Autumn, pp. 44, 46, 48-49: "Looking at the Cat's Balls," "the death of an idiot," "my friend, Andre" and "5 dollars." 1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - The New York Quarterly, #13, Winter, pp. 62-64: "Love," "back ups" and "the giraffes." 1973 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - The New York Quarterly, #14, Spring, pp. 92-93: "the icecream people," "Man Mowing the Lawn Across the Way from Me" and letter from C.B. to William Packard (editor). 1973 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - The New York Quarterly, #15, Summer, pp. 78, 80-81, 83: "Contributors," "laugh literary," "Woman in the Supermarket" and "200 Yards from the Surf." 1973 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - The New York Quarterly, #16, p. 63: "The Avoidance of Boredom." 1974 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - The New York Quarterly, #17, p. 62: "I Have Taken the Place of the Starving Artist I Used to Be (for Charles Bukowski). 1975 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - The New York Quarterly, #18, pp. 48, 50-51: "poems," "sailing up your yellow river" and "big grey balloon things, heavy." 1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - The New York Quarterly, #19, pp. 35, 102: "Who in Hell is Tom Jones?" and announcements of poetry awards. 1977 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - The New York Quarterly, #20, p. 35: "Love" and letter from C.B. to William Packard (editor). 1978 (Box 14, Folder 19)